So when you're on the My Course page
obviously you've got your unit one, two
and three, which is Word Processing,
Presentation and Spreadsheet Software.
Now, as you work through each of the
sessions, you will encounter some videos.
And I'm just going to jump
to session three of Word
Processing, just to demonstrate.
And on session three, page
two, there is a video.
Now what the videos do, they're
basically going over the information
that you've covered in the
activities and the information
that you've read in that session.
So, the video on this page is
relating to paragraph editing.
So rather than just watch the
video, you also have the opportunity
to actually carry out the tasks
yourself within the same document
that is used within the video.
To access the document, all you would
need to do is click on the practice
documents and download that and save it
in a suitable location on your computer.
You can then watch the video and
then go and open the document
and carry out the activities.
Or you could actually open the
document and work alongside the video.
So as you work through each
of the sessions, you will
encounter several videos.
There will be a video relating
to the basic text editing
tools, which is on page one.
So, again, there's another
practice file there.
There may be videos where there
isn't a new practice file, but it's
asking you to do more formatting
or make more changes in an existing
practice file that you've downloaded.
This will be made clear within the video.
So that was word processing.
You will also find these when you go to
the PowerPoint and the spreadsheet units.
Exactly the same, in presentations
when you go to a session.
So session three in presentations, there's
various videos relating to importing
spreadsheet data and creating a chart.
So again, you'd watch the video and
then you can download the spreadsheet
document, which you can then practice on
importing a chart into your PowerPoint.